<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reference on Sensu Docs</title>
    <link>/uchiwa/latest/reference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reference on Sensu Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/uchiwa/latest/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aggregates</title>
      <link>/uchiwa/latest/reference/aggregates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uchiwa/latest/reference/aggregates/</guid>
      <description>To understand aggregates in Sensu, please refer yourself to the Sensu documentation.
List All Aggregates To view all aggregates, head over to the aggregates view.
View An Aggregate To see the detail of a specific aggregate, click on it from the aggregates view. From there, you can see the check and client members, in addition to the results of every check members.
Delete An Aggregate It&amp;rsquo;s currently impossible to delete an aggregate from Uchiwa, but we would love to have you contribute to Uchiwa by implementing this feature!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checks</title>
      <link>/uchiwa/latest/reference/checks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uchiwa/latest/reference/checks/</guid>
      <description>To understand checks in Sensu, please refer yourself to the Sensu documentation.
List All Checks To view all checks, head over to the checks view. Please note that standalone checks that are not installed on the Sensu Server will not be displayed.
Issue A Check Request You can force a check request across a datacenter by selecting one or multiple checks on the checks view and clicking on the Issue Check Request action within the Bulk Actions dropdown menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clients</title>
      <link>/uchiwa/latest/reference/clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uchiwa/latest/reference/clients/</guid>
      <description>To understand clients in Sensu, please refer yourself to the Sensu documentation.
List All Clients To view all clients, including Sensu proxy clients (formerly known as &amp;ldquo;Just-in-time&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;JIT&amp;rdquo; clients), head over to the clients view.
View A Client To see the detail of a specific client, click on it from the clients view. From there, you can see the client data of the left panel and the check results data on the right one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>/uchiwa/latest/reference/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uchiwa/latest/reference/events/</guid>
      <description>To understand events in Sensu, please refer yourself to the Sensu documentation.
List All Events To view all events, head over to the events view.
View An Event To see the detail of a specific event, click on it from the events view.
Resolve An Event You can resolve an event by selecting one or multiple events on the events view and clicking on the Resolve action within the Bulk Actions dropdown menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silencing</title>
      <link>/uchiwa/latest/reference/silencing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uchiwa/latest/reference/silencing/</guid>
      <description>Follow these instructions to silence or unsilence an element.
Silence a check Across a datacenter You can silence a check for a given datacenter by selecting one or multiple checks on the checks view and clicking on the Silence/Unsilence action within the Bulk Actions dropdown menu.
For a particular client Access the client view for this client and click on the silence icon corresponding to the check on the right panel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
