<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Featured Integrations on Sensu Docs</title>
    <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Featured Integrations on Sensu Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ansible integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/ansible/</guid>
      <description>COMMERCIAL FEATURE: Access the Sensu Ansible Handler integration in the packaged Sensu Go distribution. For more information, read Get started with commercial features.
The Sensu Ansible Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that launches Ansible Tower job templates for automated remediation based on Sensu observability event data.
NOTE: The Sensu Ansible Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s auto-remediation integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/chef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/chef/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu Chef Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that deletes a Sensu entity with a failing keepalive check when the entity&amp;rsquo;s corresponding Chef node no longer exists.
NOTE: The Sensu Chef Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s deregistration integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features Use Sensu annotations to override Sensu entity names with corresponding Chef node names. Keep your sensitive API authentication information secure with Sensu environment variables and secrets management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EC2 integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/aws-ec2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/aws-ec2/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu EC2 Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that checks an AWS EC2 instance and removes it from Sensu if it is not in one of the specified states.
NOTE: The Sensu EC2 Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s deregistration integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features Tunable arguments: use Sensu annotations to set custom instance ID, instance ID labels, timeouts, and more in EC2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elasticsearch integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/elasticsearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/elasticsearch/</guid>
      <description>COMMERCIAL FEATURE: Access the Sensu Elasticsearch Handler integration in the packaged Sensu Go distribution. For more information, read Get started with commercial features.
The Sensu Elasticsearch Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that sends observation data from Sensu events and metrics to Elasticsearch. With this handler, the Sensu observation data you send to Elasticsearch is available for indexing and visualization in Kibana.
NOTE: The Sensu Elasticsearch Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s time-series and long-term event storage integrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/email/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/email/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu Email Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that sends email alerts based on your event data. With this handler, Sensu can send email messages to the email addresses you specify based on event data generated by your Sensu checks.
NOTE: The Sensu Email Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s alerting integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features The Sensu Email Handler plugin supports the login authentication mechanisms required for use with Google Mail, Office 365, and other standards-based email providers and transports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphite integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/graphite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/graphite/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu Graphite Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that sends Sensu metrics to the time-series database Graphite so you can store, instrument, and visualize Sensu metrics data.
NOTE: The Sensu Graphite Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s time-series and long-term event storage integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features Transform metrics to Graphite format: extract and transform the metrics you collect from different sources in formats like Influx, Nagios, and OpenTSDB and populate them into Graphite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InfluxDB integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/influxdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/influxdb/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu InfluxDB Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that sends Sensu metrics to the time-series database InfluxDB so you can store, instrument, and visualize Sensu metrics data. You can also use the Sensu InfluxDB Handler integration to create metrics from Sensu status check results for long-term storage in InfluxDB.
NOTE: The Sensu InfluxDB Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s time-series and long-term event storage integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jira integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/jira/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/jira/</guid>
      <description>COMMERCIAL FEATURE: Access the Sensu Jira Handler integration in the packaged Sensu Go distribution. For more information, read Get started with commercial features.
The Sensu Jira Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that creates and updates Jira issues based on observation data from Sensu events.
NOTE: The Sensu Jira Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s alerting and incident management integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenTSDB integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/opentsdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/opentsdb/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu OpenTSDB Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that sends Sensu metrics to an OpenTSDB server via its Telnet-style API. This allows you to extract, tag, and store Sensu metrics data in an OpenTSDB database.
NOTE: The Sensu OpenTSDB Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s time-series and long-term event storage integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features Transform metrics to OpenTSDB format: extract and transform the metrics you collect from different sources in formats like Graphite, Influx, and Nagios and populate them into OpenTSDB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PagerDuty integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/pagerduty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/pagerduty/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu PagerDuty Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that manages PagerDuty incidents and operator alerts. With this handler, Sensu can trigger and resolve PagerDuty incidents according to the PagerDuty schedules, notifications, and escalation, response, and orchestration workflows you already have configured.
NOTE: The Sensu PagerDuty Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s alerting and incident management integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features Optional severity mapping: match Sensu check statuses with PagerDuty incident severities via a JSON document.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prometheus integrations</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/prometheus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/prometheus/</guid>
      <description>Sensu has two Prometheus plugins: the Prometheus Collector and the Prometheus Pushgateway Handler. Both help you get Sensu observability data into Prometheus.
NOTE: The Sensu Prometheus plugins are examples of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s time-series and long-term event storage integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Sensu Prometheus Collector The Sensu Prometheus Collector plugin is a Sensu check that collects metrics from a Prometheus exporter or the Prometheus query API and outputs the metrics to stdout in Influx, Graphite, or JSON format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puppet integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/puppet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/puppet/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu Puppet Keepalive Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that deletes a Sensu entity with a failing keepalive check when the entity&amp;rsquo;s corresponding Puppet node no longer exists or is deregistered.
NOTE: The Sensu Puppet Keepalive Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s deregistration integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features Use Sensu annotations to override Sensu entity names with corresponding Puppet node names. Keep sensitive API authentication information secure with Sensu environment variables and secrets management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rundeck integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/rundeck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/rundeck/</guid>
      <description>COMMERCIAL FEATURE: Access the Sensu Rundeck Handler integration in the packaged Sensu Go distribution. For more information, read Get started with commercial features.
The Sensu Rundeck Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that initiates Rundeck jobs for automated remediation based on Sensu event data.
NOTE: The Sensu Rundeck Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s auto-remediation integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features The Sensu Rundeck Handler plugin supports both Rundeck Enterprise and Rundeck Open Source and standard job invocation or webhook invocation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SaltStack integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/saltstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/saltstack/</guid>
      <description>COMMERCIAL FEATURE: Access the Sensu SaltStack Handler integration in the packaged Sensu Go distribution. For more information, read Get started with commercial features.
The Sensu SaltStack Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that launches SaltStack functions for automated remediation based on Sensu event data.
NOTE: The Sensu SaltStack Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s auto-remediation integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features The Sensu SaltStack Handler plugin supports both SaltStack Enterprise and SaltStack Open Source as well as SaltStack functions such as service, state, saltutil, and grains (including arg and kwarg arguments).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/servicenow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/servicenow/</guid>
      <description>COMMERCIAL FEATURE: Access the Sensu ServiceNow Handler integration in the packaged Sensu Go distribution. For more information, read Get started with commercial features.
The Sensu ServiceNow Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that creates and updates ServiceNow incidents and events based on observation data from Sensu events.
NOTE: The Sensu ServiceNow Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s alerting and incident management integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slack integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/slack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/slack/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu Slack Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that sends alerts based on your event data. With this handler, Sensu can trigger alerts to the Slack channels you specify based on event data generated by your Sensu checks.
NOTE: The Sensu Slack Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s alerting and incident management integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features Use event-based templating to include observation data from event attributes in your alerts to add meaningful, actionable context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sumo Logic integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/sumologic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/sumologic/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu Sumo Logic Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that sends Sensu observability events and metrics to a Sumo Logic HTTP Logs and Metrics Source. This handler sends Sensu events as log entries, a set of metrics, or both, depending on the mode of operation you specify.
NOTE: The Sensu Sumo Logic Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s time-series and long-term event storage integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TimescaleDB integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/timescaledb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/timescaledb/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu TimescaleDB Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that sends Sensu metrics to the time-series database TimescaleDB so you can store, instrument, and visualize Sensu metrics data.
NOTE: The Sensu TimescaleDB Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s time-series and long-term event storage integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features Transform metrics to TimescaleDB format: extract and transform the metrics you collect from different sources in formats like Graphite, OpenTSDB, Nagios, and Influx and populate them into TimescaleDB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wavefront integration</title>
      <link>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/wavefront/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sensu-go/6.6/plugins/featured-integrations/wavefront/</guid>
      <description>The Sensu Wavefront Handler plugin is a Sensu handler that sends Sensu metrics to Wavefront via a proxy, which allows you to store, instrument, and visualize Sensu metrics data in an Wavefront database.
NOTE: The Sensu Wavefront Handler plugin is an example of Sensu&amp;rsquo;s time-series and long-term event storage integrations. To find more integrations, search Bonsai, the Sensu asset hub.
Features Transform metrics to Wavefront format: extract and transform the metrics you collect from different sources in formats like Graphite, OpenTSDB, Nagios, and Influx and populate them into Wavefront.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
